Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-118 (1970: June 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-119 (1970: June 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-120 (1970: June 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-121 (1970: June 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-122 (1970: June 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: no.70-123 (1970: June 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-124 (1970: July 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-125 (1970: July 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-126 (1970: July 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-127 (1970: July 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-128 (1970: July 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-129 (1970: July 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-130 (1970: July 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-131 (1970: July 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-132 (1970: July 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-133 (1970: July 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-134 (1970: July 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-135 (1970: July 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-136 (1970: July 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-137 (1970: July 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-138 (1970: July 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-139 (1970: July 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-140 (1970: July 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-141 (1970: July 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-142 (1970: July 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-143 (1970: July 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-144 (1970: July 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: no.70-145 (1970: July 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-146 (1970: Aug. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-147 (1970: Aug. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-148 (1970: Aug. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-149 (1970: Aug. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-150 (1970: Aug. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-151 (1970: Aug. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-152 (1970: Aug. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-153 (1970: Aug. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-154 (1970: Aug. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-155 (1970: Aug. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-156 (1970: Aug. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-157 (1970: Aug. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-158 (1970: Aug. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-159 (1970: Aug. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-160 (1970: Aug. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-161 (1970: Aug. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-162 (1970: Aug. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-163 (1970: Aug. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-164 (1970: Aug. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-165 (1970: Aug. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: no.70-166 (1970: Aug. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-167 (1970: Sep. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-168 (1970: Sep. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-169 (1970: Sep. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-170 (1970: Sep. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-171 (1970: Sep. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-171 (1970: Sep. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-172 (1970: Sep. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-173 (1970: Sep. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-174 (1970: Sep. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-175 (1970: Sep. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-176 (1970: Sep. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-177 (1970: Sep. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-178 (1970: Sep. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-179 (1970: Sep. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-180 (1970: Sep. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-181 (1970: Sep. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-182 (1970: Sep. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-183 (1970: Sep. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-184 (1970: Sep. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-185 (1970: Sep. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: no.70-186 (1970: Sep. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-187 (1970: Oct. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-188 (1970: Oct. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-189 (1970: Oct. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-190 (1970: Oct. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-191 (1970: Oct. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-192 (1970: Oct. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-193 (1970: Oct. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-194 (1970: Oct. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-195 (1970: Oct. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-196 (1970: Oct. 15/16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-197 (1970: Oct. 19)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-198 (1970: Oct. 20)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-199 (1970: Oct. 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-200 (1970: Oct. 22)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-201 (1970: Oct. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-202 (1970: Oct. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-203 (1970: Oct. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-204 (1970: Oct. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-205 (1970: Oct. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: no.70-206 (1970: Oct. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-207 (1970: Nov. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-208 (1970: Nov. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-209 (1970: Nov. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-210 (1970: Nov. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-211 (1970: Nov. 9)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-212 (1970: Nov. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-213 (1970: Nov. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-214 (1970: Nov. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-215 (1970: Nov. 16)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-216 (1970: Nov. 17)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-217 (1970: Nov. 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-218 (1970: Nov. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-219 (1970: Nov. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-220 (1970: Nov. 23)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-221 (1970: Nov. 24)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-222 (1970: Nov. 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-223 (1970: Nov. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: no.70-224 (1970: Nov. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-225 (1970: Dec. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-226 (1970: Dec. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-227 (1970: Dec. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-228 (1970: Dec. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-229 (1970: Dec. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-230 (1970: Dec. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-231 (1970: Dec. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-232 (1970: Dec. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-233 (1970: Dec. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-234 (1970: Dec. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-235 (1970: Dec. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-236 (1970: Dec. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-237 (1970: Dec. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-238 (1970: Dec. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-239 (1970: Dec. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-240 (1970: Dec. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-241 (1970: Dec. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-242 (1970: Dec. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-243 (1970: Dec. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: no.70-244 (1970: Dec. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-1 (1971: Jan. 4)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-2 (1971: Jan. 5)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-3 (1971: Jan. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-4 (1971: Jan. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-5 (1971: Jan. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-6 (1971: Jan. 11)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-7 (1971: Jan. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-8 (1971: Jan. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-9 (1971: Jan. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-10 (1971: Jan. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-11 (1971: Jan. 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-12 (1971: Jan. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-13 (1971: Jan. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-14 (1971: Jan. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-15 (1971: Jan. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-16 (1971: Jan. 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-17 (1971: Jan. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-18 (1971: Jan. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.71-19 (1971: Jan. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-21 (1971: Feb. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-22 (1971: Feb. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-23 (1971: Feb. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-24 (1971: Feb. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-25 (1971: Feb. 5)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-26 (1971: Feb. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-27 (1971: Feb. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-28 (1971: Feb. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-29 (1971: Feb. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-30 (1971: Feb. 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-31 (1971: Feb. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-32 (1971: Feb. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-33 (1971: Feb. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-34 (1971: Feb. 22)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-35 (1971: Feb. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-36 (1971: Feb. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-37 (1971: Feb. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.71-38 (1971: Feb. 26)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-39 (1971: Mar. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-40 (1971: Mar. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-41 (1971: Mar. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-42 (1971: Mar. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-43 (1971: Mar. 5)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-44 (1971: Mar. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-45 (1971: Mar. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-46 (1971: Mar. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-47 (1971: Mar. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-48 (1971: Mar. 12)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-49 (1971: Mar. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-50 (1971: Mar. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-51 (1971: Mar. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-52 (1971: Mar. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-53 (1971: Mar. 19)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-54 (1971: Mar. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-55 (1971: Mar. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-56 (1971: Mar. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-57 (1971: Mar. 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-58 (1971: Mar. 26)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-59 (1971: Mar. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-60 (1971: Mar. 30)
  - Item 23: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.71-61 (1971: Mar. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-62 (1971: Apr. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-63 (1971: Apr. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-64 (1971: Apr. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-65 (1971: Apr. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-66 (1971: Apr. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-67 (1971: Apr. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-68 (1971: Apr. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-69 (1971: Apr. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-70 (1971: Apr. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-71 (1971: Apr. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-72 (1971: Apr. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-73 (1971: Apr. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-74 (1971: Apr. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-75 (1971: Apr. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-76 (1971: Apr. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-77 (1971: Apr. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-78 (1971: Apr. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-79 (1971: Apr. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-80 (1971: Apr. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-81 (1971: Apr. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.71-82 (1971: Apr. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-83 (1971: May 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-84 (1971: May 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-85 (1971: May 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-86 (1971: May 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-87 (1971: May 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-88 (1971: May 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-89 (1971: May 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-90 (1971: May 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-91 (1971: May 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-92 (1971: May 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-93 (1971: May 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-94 (1971: May 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-95 (1971: May 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-96 (1971: May 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-97 (1971: May 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-98 (1971: May 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-99 (1971: May 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-100 (1971: May 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-101 (1971: May 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.71-102 (1971: May 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-103 (1971: June 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-104 (1971: June 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-106 (1971: June 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-107 (1971: June 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-108 (1971: June 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-109 (1971: June 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-110 (1971: June 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-111 (1971: June 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-112 (1971: June 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-113 (1971: June 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-114 (1971: June 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-115 (1971: June 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-116 (1971: June 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-117 (1971: June 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-118 (1971: June 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-119 (1971: June 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-120 (1971: June 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-121 (1971: June 29)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.71-122 (1971: June 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)